https://ibbdesign.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyHome-Privacy Policy-Your privacy is very important to us. As a result, we have created this privacy policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, or disclose your data. Our privacy policy is outlined below for your review.Who we areIBB Design Fine Furnishings is a full-service fine furnishings boutique and design firm know for offering high-quality furnishings for over 39 years! Our website address is: https://ibbdesign.com.What personal data we collect and why we collect itWe collect the information that you provide to us. Before or at the time of collecting your personal information, we will identify and disclose why we are collecting the information and will only use that information to fulfill our disclosed objective unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned. We retain that personal information as long as needed to fulfill the disclosed objective. We will collect the information by lawful and fair means and will do our best to maintain the personal data with reasonable security safeguards against unauthorized disclosure, copying or use. We will continue to make our policies available to our customers.CommentsWhen visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.MediaIf you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.Contact / Subscription formsWe ask for basic contact information from you in our forms in order to contact you back and address any comments or concerns that you may have when contacting us. The type of information that we collect depends on the form that you are completing; however, none of the information provided will be used outside our already stated purposes.CookiesIf you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.Embedded content from other websitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.Who we share your data withYour data may be shared with third party payment processing and payment gateways to complete your purchase such as PayPal. Your information is encrypted and will only be stored long enough to complete the transaction. Any additional third party providers used by us will only collect, use, or disclose your personal information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us. All of these third party services and partners have their own privacy policies, so we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these service providers.How long we retain your dataIf you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.What rights you have over your dataIf you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.You can withdraw your consent and opt out of all communication by unsubscribing from our emails, or contacting us at info@ibbdesign.com.Where we send your dataVisitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service. We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so if you violate our Terms of Service.IBB Design Contact informationFor additional information or to inquire further, please email us at web@ibbdesign.com. You can visit our showroom at the following address:IBB Design Fine Furnishings | 5798 Genesis Court, Frisco, TX  75034 | 214-618-6600We may update this policy as needed at the sole discretion of IBB Design.Updated May 29, 2019 For policy information on returns and shipping, please click here to view online orders policy.FOUR-TIME WINNER OF “BEST FURNITURE STORE IN THE COUNTRY” – VISIT THE STORE AND SHOP OUR IN-STOCK DESIGNER FURNISHINGS AVAILABLE FOR IMMEDIATE DELIVERY.
